uberhumor.com 2019-10-18

# Privacy Policy | Funny Pictures, Quotes, Pics, Photos, Images. Videos of Really Very Cute animals.

    **Revised: August 5, 2019**

    **** This Privacy Policy explains how UberHumor.com and UberHumor.com’s third-party
    advertising company Intermarkets (collectively “UberHumor.com” “We,” and/or “Us” ), collect,
    use, and share information from or about you when you use our website (“Website”), emails, and
    other digital products, including any online or mobile website, application (“app”), or other
    digital product or service installation through which this Privacy Policy appears (each a
    “Service,” collectively the “Services”), that may display interactive advertisements.
    Your privacy is important to us, and we are committed to protecting the personal information
    you share with us. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, protect, and share
    information when you are served an advertisement using or visiting the Services. This Privacy
    Policy also explains your choices for managing your information preferences.
    By using the Services, you consent to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to
    the practices of third parties that UberHumor.com does not own, control, manage, or employ.
    This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our Website and not to
    information collected offline.
    UberHumor.com uses the following ad servers and their privacy policies can be found by
    clicking on their names below:
    
    AppNexus [https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy]
    DFP [https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/ ]
    LiveIntent [https://liveintent.com/services-privacy-policy]
    Spot.IM [https://www.spot.im/privacy]
    
    While we are not a member, we are committed to following the Network Advertising Initiative’s
    Self-Regulatory Principles. [LINK IS: https://www.networkadvertising.org/code-enforcement]

    **Information We Collect through the Services**

    **Personally Identifiable Information:**
    We may collect information that personally identifies you, such as your name, username, email
    address, credit card details, and other information as we may from time to time request at our
    discretion (“Personally Identifiable Information” or “PII”) if you choose to share such
    information with us. For example, you may be asked to provide us with certain Personally
    
    UberHumor.com
    Privacy Policy Update
    
    2
    Identifiable Information when you register with or use our Services, sign up for an email
    subscription, and at other times. The decision to provide this information is optional; however, if
    you elect not to register with or provide such information, you may not be able to access certain
    content, features, or services available on or through the Services. We reserve the right to send
    you certain communications relating to the UberHumor.com service, such as service
    announcements, administrative messages, special promotions, and UberHumor.com newsletters,
    which are considered part of your account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of
    receiving them. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, financials, etc.) will
    not be stored on our servers.

    **Non-Personally Identifiable Information:**

    We automatically collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information when you use the Site. Non-
    Personally Identifiable Information includes demographic information (such as age, gender, city
    or state) and a user’s click stream information. Click stream data is anonymous and can include
    information such as your IP address, webpages viewed, the date and time at which those pages
    were viewed and interaction with content and advertisements on those webpages. Technologies
    used to collect this click stream data include cookies and web beacons. UberHumor.com collects
    Non-Personally Identifiable Information and stores it in log files. We use this information to help
    us understand how people use our Site. For example, each time you use the Website we
    automatically collect the type of web browser you use, your operating system, your ISP, which
    pages you view, and the time and duration of your visits to the Site.
    We may supplement our click stream data with Non-Personally Identifiable Information
    (namely, behavioral and demographic data from third party Services Providers as defined below)
    to target and serve some of the advertisements you see on the Services. This anonymous
    supplemental data may include such things as zip code, age, gender, and income range. We use
    the Non-Personally Identifiable Information described above to better customize the sort of
    advertisements you see. This information also may be used to help measure and research an
    advertisement’s effectiveness, or for other purposes. We also aggregate anonymous cookie data
    in order to identify large audience segments that assist advertisers in targeting their campaigns to
    the most relevant Internet audience.
    While we encourage third party advertising providers to comply with applicable law and self-
    regulatory standards, there are far too many online advertising transactions occurring on our
    Website to police every transaction. We pass through all advertising disclosures and opt-out
    mechanisms of the advertising providers, but the use and collection of information by our third-
    party advertising Service Providers is governed by the individual privacy policies of those
    providers.

    **Social Media Information:**

    **** If you visit the Services on a device on which you also use social networks or if you interact with
    us through a social media service or other platform, we may have access to some information
    you provide to that social network or platform such as your name, email address, friend list,
    photo, age, gender, location, birthday, social networking ID, current city, and the people/sites
    you follow, or your posts or “likes.” For a description on how social media services and other

    third-party platforms, plug-ins, integrations or applications handle your information, please refer
    to their respective privacy policies and terms of use, which may permit you to modify your
    privacy settings.

    **Cookies and Web Beacons:**
    We may use cookies (a small text file placed on your computer to identify your computer and
    browser), web beacons (an electronic file placed on a website that monitors usage), and other
    similar technologies to improve the quality of the Services and to better target and analyze
    consumer behavior with the goal of providing better and more relevant advertising. Our cookie
    does not include your name or anything personal to you. It simply tells us that we have
    encountered your computer at some prior point. Most web browsers are initially set up to accept
    cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being
    sent. However, certain features of the Services may not work if you delete or disable cookies.
    Alternatively, you are always free to opt out of the cookies.
    Some of our Service Providers may use their own cookies and web beacons in connection with
    the services they perform on our behalf. If you would like more information about these practices
    and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please
    click here. [LINK is: https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/]
    
    **How We Use and Share Information Collected through the Services**
    **General:**
    We use Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information for
    internal purposes only, such as to notify you of new products or services, to send service
    notifications, to customize the advertising and content you see, to offer email promotions from
    our trusted network of partners (which you may opt-out of at any time, as described more fully
    below), to fulfill your requests for products and services, to improve the Services, to conduct
    research, to solicit your feedback and input about the Services, and to provide more relevant and
    effective products, services, and advertisements on or through the Services.
    Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information may be
    combined with data collected from other sources so that we may further improve the relevance
    and effectiveness of products, services, and advertisements offered on or through the Services.
    We will not sell, share, or rent Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally
    Identifiable Information to third parties, and we will not otherwise disclose Personally
    Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information to third parties, without
    your permission, except as expressly disclosed in this Privacy Policy.
    
    **Service Providers:**
    UberHumor.com may share Personally Identifiable Information with its service providers that
    help UberHumor.com provide the services that you request (“Service Providers”). For example,

    we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as credit card
    processing, advertising, analytics tools, data management services, web hosting, and web
    development. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform
    these services, however, each Service Provider must agree to implement and maintain reasonable
    security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information involved in order
    to protect your information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or
    disclosure.

    **Non-Personally Identifiable Information Only:**
    We may use, and disclose to third parties, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information
    regarding the Website (e.g., number of visits, page views, and the like) without your permission.
    However, such information does not identify you individually.
    
    **Other Transfers:**
    We may share Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information
    with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with UberHumor.com. If
    UberHumor.com is merged, acquired, or sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our
    assets, we may disclose or transfer Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally
    Identifiable Information in connection with such transaction. You will have the opportunity to
    opt out of any such transfer if, in our discretion, the new entity plans to handle your information
    in a way that differs materially from this Privacy Policy.
    
    **Third Party Sharing:**
    We may use, and disclose to third parties, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information
    regarding the Website (e.g., number of visits, page views, and the like) without your permission.
    However, such information does not identify you individually. As for Personally Identifiable
    Information, we may share your first name, email address, and zip code with our trusted network
    of partners. However, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of sharing such
    information.
    
    **Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement:**
    UberHumor.com cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties
    to enforce and comply with the law. UberHumor.com reserves the right to disclose Personally
    Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information to government or law
    enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or
    appropriate in order to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to
    protect the safety, property or rights of UberHumor.com or of any third party, to prevent or stop
    any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

    **Opt-Out of Third Party Sharing of Personal Information:**

    **Email Opt-Out Procedure:**
    IF YOU DO NOT WANT TO RECEIVE EMAIL PROMOTIONS FROM OUR TRUSTED
    NETWORK OF PARTNERS, YOU MAY UNSUBSCRIBE FROM OUR EMAIL
    NEWSLETTERS OR PROMOTIONAL EMAILS BY FOLLOWING THE OPT-OUT
    INSTRUCTIONS CONTAINED IN THE EMAIL OR EMAIL US AT
    ADMIN@UBERHUMOR.COM AND YOU WILL BE REMOVED FROM OUR THIRD-
    PARTY DISCLOSURE LIST.
    Once a request to opt out has been received, UberHumor.com will send a confirming email
    message to the user that the user’s Personally Identifiable Information has been successfully
    opted out of UberHumor.com’s database. If you do not receive this confirmatory email, then
    please contact us to ensure that your request was received and processed.
    
    **Cookie Opt-Out Procedure:**
    UberHumor.com and our service providers may use the information we collect from and about
    you to deliver relevant ads to you when you use the Services (on any of your devices) or another
    service. As noted above, third-party advertising networks and advertisers may use cookies and
    similar technologies to collect and track information such as demographic information, inferred
    interests, aggregated information, and information the different devices you use and your activity
    on such devices, to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests.
    To find out more about interest-based advertising and third-party entities that use these
    technologies, please go to https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-
    advertising/.
    IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO OPT-OUT OF INTEREST-BASED ADVERTISING, PLEASE
    VISIT HTTP://WWW.NETWORKADVERTISING.ORG/CHOICES 
    OR HTTP://WWW.ABOUTADS.INFO.
    PLEASE NOTE that if you erase or otherwise alter your browser’s cookie file (including
    upgrading certain browsers) you may need to opt out again.
    PLEASE NOTE that opting out of the interest-based ad-serving cookie does not mean that you
    will stop seeing either pop up advertising or banner ads embedded in websites. You can control
    many pop ups by using free software available on the Internet or by disabling JavaScript on your
    browser. UberHumor.com has no control over the use or frequency of pop-up ads employed by
    website publishers or software manufacturers.
    
    **Mobile Opt-Out Procedure:**
    We also sometimes use, or partner with publishers, publisher-facing, or app developer platforms
    that use mobile Software Development Kits (“SDKs”), or use an SDK with a mobile app that we
    offer, to collect Information, such as mobile identifiers (e.g., IDFAs and Android Advertising
    IDs), and information connected to how mobile devices interact with our Services and those
    using our Services. A mobile SDK is the mobile app version of a web beacon (see “Web

    Beacons” above). The SDK is a bit of computer code that app developers can include in their
    apps to enable ads to be shown, data to be collected, and related services or analytics to be
    performed. We may use this technology to deliver or help our Partners deliver certain advertising
    through mobile applications and browsers based on information associated with your mobile
    device.
    Depending on your device, you may be able to reset your mobile device&#39;s advertising identifier at
    any time by accessing the privacy settings on your mobile device. In addition, each operating
    system, iOS for Apple phones, Android for Android devices and Windows for Microsoft devices,
    provides its own instructions on how to prevent the delivery of tailored in-application
    advertisements. You may review the support materials and/or the privacy settings for the
    respective operating systems in order to opt-out of tailored in-application advertisements.
    IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO OPT-OUT OF SUCH AD NETWORKS’ AND SERVICES&#39;
    ADVERTISING PRACTICES ON THE PARTICULAR DEVICE ON WHICH YOU ARE
    ACCESSING THIS POLICY, GO TO
    HTTP://WWW.NETWORKADVERTISING.ORG/MOBILE-CHOICE  TO OPT-OUT FOR
    YOUR MOBILE WEB BROWSERS. YOU MAY ALSO DOWNLOAD THE APPCHOICES
    APP AT //WWW.ABOUTADS.INFO/APPCHOICES TO OPT-OUT IN MOBILE APPS.
    PLEASE NOTE that all Cookie and Mobile opt-out tools referenced above are provided by third
    parties, not UberHumor.com. UberHumor.com does not control or operate these tools or the
    choices that advertisers and others provide through these tools.
    
    **Third Party Websites:**
    The Services may contain links to websites or content operated and maintained by third parties.
    UberHumor.com does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from
    our practices. If you click on a link or an advertisement, the privacy policy of the website to
    which you link will govern the collection and use of your information by that website’s
    operator(s). You access such third-party websites or content at your own risk. You should always
    read the privacy policy of a third-party website before disclosing any information to the website.
    For more information, please click here. [LINK IS:
    
    https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/]
    
    **Spyware or Adware:**
    These terms refer to applications that are downloaded to your computer. These types of
    applications deliver ads (usually in the form of pop-up type ads) based on your web usage. We
    do not participate in any way with spyware or adware applications, and we do not download
    these types (or any types) of applications without your expressed acceptance. Cookies and .swf
    files are not spyware or adware, and they are not harmful to your computer.
    
    **Public Forums:**

    Please be advised that, whenever you voluntarily post information to any UberHumor.com
    community page or any other public forums, such information can and may be accessed by the
    public. This means that any person or entity with access to such information can potentially use
    it for any purpose, including sending unsolicited communications.
    
    **Security:**
    We recognize the importance of safeguarding the confidentiality of your information.
    Accordingly, we employ standard security measures designed to protect your information from
    unauthorized access. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be
    guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect any information you
    transmit on or through the Site, please be advised that UberHumor.com assumes no
    responsibility or liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission,
    unauthorized third-party access, or other causes beyond UberHumor.com’s reasonable control.
    
    **Processing in the United States:**
    We process and store all information in the United States. By using our Services, you agree that
    the collection, use, transfer, and disclosure of your Personally Identifiable Information will be
    governed by the applicable laws in the United States.
    **Children’s Privacy Statement:**
    The UberHumor.com Services are directed to, and intended for use by, adults only. We do not
    knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we
    have inadvertently received information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such
    information from our records. Because we do not knowingly collect any information from
    children under the age of 13, we also do not knowingly distribute such information to third
    parties.
    
    **Terms and Conditions:**
    Please also visit our Community Policy section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations
    of liability governing the use of our Website at [http://uberhumor.com/terms-of-use].
    
    **Privacy Policy Changes:**
    UberHumor.com may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you should review
    this Policy periodically. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by
    posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Services. Those changes will go into effect on the
    Revision Date shown at the top of the revised Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Services
    constitutes your consent to the revised Privacy Policy.
    
    **Acceptance of Privacy Policy:**

    When you use the UberHumor.com Services, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this
    Privacy Policy, and UberHumor.com will have the right to use your information as described in
    this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to have your information used in any of the ways
    described in this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use of the UberHumor.com Services. You
    can also access, correct, or change your Personally Identifiable Information, or opt-out of our
    direct marketing efforts, by sending an email to admin@uberhumor.com. Once a request to opt
    out has been received, UberHumor.com will send a confirming email message to the user that the
    user’s Personally Identifiable Information has been successfully opted out of UberHumor.com’s
    database. If you do not receive this confirmatory email, then please contact us to ensure that your
    request was received and processed. If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy,
    please email us at admin@uberhumor.com.
    
    **California Privacy Notice:**
    California’s Shine the Light law provides California residents with the right to receive
    disclosures about any sharing of their personal information with other companies.
    If you are a California resident and you provided your personal information to UberHumor.com,
    then, once each calendar year, you may submit a written request for information about the
    information we shared, if any, with other companies for their use in direct marketing. To submit
    your written request, please email us at admin@uberhumor.com with “Request for California
    Privacy” in the subject line.
    Within 30 days of receiving your request, we will send you a list of the categories of personal
    information disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the
    immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties.
    We reserve our right not to respond to requests sent more than once in a calendar year, or
    requests submitted to an address other than the one posted in this notice.
    Please note that the California Shine the Light law does not cover all information sharing. Our
    disclosure only includes information covered by the law.
    
    **Users in the EEA and Switzerland**
    If you are a resident of the EEA or Switzerland, the following information applies with respect to
    personal data collected through your use of our Services.

    **Purposes of processing and legal basis for processing:**
    We process personal data consistent with our disclosures in this Privacy Policy. We process
    personal data on the following legal bases: (1) with your consent; (2) as necessary to perform our
    agreement to provide the Services; and (3) as necessary for our legitimate interests in providing
    the Services where those interests do not override your fundamental rights and freedoms related
    to data privacy.

    **Transfers:**
    Personal data we collect may be transferred to, and stored and processed in, the United States or
    any other country in which we or our affiliates or processors maintain facilities. We will ensure
    that transfers of personal data to a third country or an international organization are subject to
    appropriate safeguards.

    **Individual Rights:**
    If you are a resident of the EEA or Switzerland, we respect your rights according to Chapter 3 of
    the EU General Data Protection Regulation. In order to verify your identity, we may require you
    to provide us with personal information prior to accessing any records containing information
    about you.

    **Contacting Us**
    If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information
    below.
    
    https://www.UberHumor.com/contact/
    
    uberhumor.jay@gmail.com

To change your privacy settings, click here
